http://www.costume-shop.com/pages/the-costume-shop-privacy-police

Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for The Costume Shop. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill and ship your order.
If you have not requested to be part of our mailing list we will never send you promotional emails
Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information such as credit card data, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. All pages on our site run on "https" as noted by the lock you will see before the URL.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to process orders and contact you are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment and only the last 4 digits of your credit card can be viewed by anyone in our organization.
Added to your cart:
Cart subtotal
